Hello everyone, this is Minami Mizuhashi.
I'm Minami Mizuhashi.
I'm Minami Minami. I'm Minami Minami.
We are Emma
This is Emma.
A-ha-ha-ha-ha...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
We are here in Hong Kong!
This time, the three of us are here to promote our concert in Hong Kong in June.
We've been here for 3 days!
So we had a lot of interviews
We hope to have a nice trip
We hope to have a wonderful trip!
Well then, I'm off to Hong Kong!
Bye bye!
Ta-da! I'm here at Sony Music in Hong Kong!
Today is my first day here, and I'll be doing a lot of interviews, and I'd like to talk to you now.
Good luck!
Hello! Super-class recommendation!
Today, we had the pleasure of having you at the Japanese Women's Union Live!
Se-no!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Cheese!
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We are pleased to announce that Nogizaka46 Live in Hong Kong 2024 will be held on June 28th!
Yes, sir.
Knock yourself out.
Nogizaka46.
46.
Thank you very much.
We're done.
We got waffles after the first day's interview, so let's eat them!
They look delicious!
They're waiting for us.
My senior's appetite!
Stop it! Don't do this.
I put it in my study.
Delicious.
Crunchy on the outside.
The inside is sticky.
Remi sponge cake, really.
It's really good.
Lemi Castella.
Now...
I'm going to meet someone.
I'm going.
I can already see them.
I'm nervous.
He's so cute.
Hello. - Hello.
Hello, please.
Hello.
Hello. - Hello.
Good afternoon.
Good day to you
nice to meet you
Yes, sir.
Next.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Today we have JUSTORI.
Everyone, enjoy nature and life.
Good night, everyone.
Today we had the freshest and most enjoyable day in Japan.
COMPLEMENT to more 100% variety.
Good night.
Good night!
Here I am!
I'm still in my uniform.
I thought you all looked the same.
dressmaker
I'll grab it. grasp
Here we are today.
Friends in Hong Kong
We have a lot of interviews today.
We're going to see some of the tourist attractions in Hong Kong.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to have fun and do my best today.
I'll do my best.
I'm off!
Cute lady!
VQ.
Okay.
Please.
Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
Please.
Good night.
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Bon appétit!
I recommend it.
I'll take it.
So cute!
Delicious!
What's your favorite chicken?
Not at all.
You like it, too.
Yes, I do.
It's not spicy.
It's good.
This way.
What does this mean? What does this mean?
Yes, what is it?
Tengu.
No, no, no...
Tengu are here in heaven.
Only a tengu would look at you.
Tengu.
Cat.
Ah!
Well...
Wow!
It's unbelievably unappealing.
The surface is so shiny!
I've never seen it like this!
Bon appétit!
Let's eat!
Looks delicious.
Yum.
Mmm. - Mmm.
It's kind of naturally sweet, isn't it?
I thought it would be sweeter.
Oh, it's not.
It's not there.
Spilled in Hong Kong.
I've spilled on my clothes two days in a row.
It's true.
I'm doing it.
I did eggs.
But Kashboro Miki...
So says Ichinose Miku.
You spilled the custard man just now.
No, I didn't.
I didn't spill it.
The custard came out on its own.
Where did you spill it?
She's doing it on her uniform. This girl is doing it in uniform, not plain clothes.
This girl is doing it in uniform, not plain clothes.
Mr. Mito will get angry.
That's right.
He'll be furious.
Come on, Miki, eat.
Wow! Eggs are big!
It's like a resort!
This is the HKCEC where we're going live.
We're coming here!
It looks so tiny in the video.
But it's so big!
Please come!
Here we are!
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for watching!
Street snapshots are all the rage on social media these days.
I never thought I'd be this nervous.
Wow!
That's amazing.
Wow, wow, wow.
That's great.
Three years, one week.
That's more than a photo shoot. Thank you for your hard work.
It is starting.
It looks like the posters are being put up now, so I think I'll go take a look.
Yes, it is quite cold inside the buildings in Hong Kong.
Yes, it is.
There is nothing but good smells in the buildings.
Smells good. That's just it.
It's work fish.
It's hot, though.
Isn't that it?
Where?
Oh, my God!
Ta-da!Ta-da!
It's big!
That's great!
Wow!
It's huge! Can you see it?
It's huge!
Oh, it's bigger than I thought.
Is this the venue?
Oh, this is the venue?
It's a room venue.
We're playing from 9:00 p.m. Japan time. At night.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Sure, it's really late if you think about it that way.
Very late.
Japan is pretty early, so the usual live show is.
Tension.
Please look for it, everyone.
Please look for them.
Please take a picture with me.
See you soon.
Yes, I did. So, my 3-day trip to Hong Kong is over.
It's over.
It got better.
We are going to have a live concert here on May 28th.
Yes, sir.
What do you think? Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
The last three days have made me more excited.
Yes, I am.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be happy if many Hong Kong fans come, and I'm sure there will be some things that will be different from what we usually do in our live performances. I would be happy if many Hong Kong fans could come, and I am sure that there will be some things that will be different from what we usually do in our live performances.
I'm sure there will be some things that will be different from what we usually do.
I'm sure it will be different from what we usually do, so please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
Good luck.
Now we are going back to Japan.
Let's go home.
Bye-bye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Bye, bye, bye.
Thank you for watching!